{
    "id": "rie",
    "name": "りえ",
    "yomi": "Rie",
    "text": [
        "40代婦人・東京在住の会社員です。<br>美術館・緑の濃い場所・神社・お花・美味しいもの・お酒が好きです。",
        "A lady in 40s, company employee in Tokyo.<br>I love: art museum, green place, shrine, flowers, delicious foods and alcohol."
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "Have you ever made a pitfall?",
            "jp": "落とし穴を作ったことある？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No i have never",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "What do you think about during a boring meeting?",
            "jp": "つまらない会議の間何を考えている？",
            "yes": "things that want to do",
            "left": "やりたいこと",
            "no": "people who love",
            "right": "好きなひとのこと"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Love is all about?",
            "jp": "愛こそ",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "すべて",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "すべてではない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "Do you believe in invisible existence?",
            "jp": "目に見えないものの存在を",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "信じる",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "信じない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "You have a trauma?",
            "jp": "トラウマが",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "ある",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "ない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "When do you fell happy?",
            "jp": "幸せを感じるのは？",
            "yes": "when being by myself",
            "left": "ひとりでいるとき",
            "no": "when being with someone",
            "right": "他の人といるとき"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "Do you drink alcohol when you are alone?",
            "jp": "ひとりでも",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "飲む",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "飲まない"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "I am",
            "jp": "自分は",
            "yes": "an adult",
            "left": "もうさすがに大人",
            "no": "still a child",
            "right": "まだぜんぜん子供"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "What do you see when you walk?",
            "jp": "歩いているときどこを見てる？",
            "yes": "a person passing by",
            "left": "向こうから来る人",
            "no": "scenery around",
            "right": "周りの景色"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "The Truth",
            "jp": "本当のこと",
            "yes": "I want to know",
            "left": "知りたい",
            "no": "I don't want to know",
            "right": "知りたくない"
        }
    ]
}